Charles D. Wrege Research Materials on Microfilm 6395 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Charles D. Wrege Research Materials on Microfilm
1841-1960
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wrege, Charles D.
6395 mf
2.5 cubic feet
10 microfilm reels
Minutes, reports, microfilm.
8691864
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 15, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, July 15, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Charles "Chuck" Wrege finished his undergraduate degree in Upsala College, obtained his Masters degree at the New School fo Social Research and another Masters of Business Administration and his Ph.D. at NYU. He taught industrial management at Rutgers University for 30 years. He became a renowned historian, researcher and writer. He is regarded as a "National Treasure" by many in his field because of his expertise and the seminal research he has done in the area of management history.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Wrege, Charles D.
8691864
- Erie Lackawanna Railway Company Deposit - Minutes of the Board of Directors -- Vol. 1, 1842-1846 to Vol. 3, 1846-1853 (Reel 1)
- Erie Lackawanna Railway Company Deposit -- Erie Railway Bd. Of Directors, Minutes - 1868-1879 - Vol. 1-Vol. 3 (Reel 2)
- Erie Lackawanna Railway Company Deposit - Erie Railway, Finance Committee Minutes - 1872-1874 (Reel 3)
- Erie Lackawanna Railway Company Deposit - Erie Railway Bd. Of Directors, Minutes -- 1868-1879 - Vol. 3-Vol. 4 (Reel 4)
- Erie Lackawanna Railway -- NY E RR/Board of Directors, Minutes - Vol. 4; NY E RR/System Map 1853; Erie RR Erie Lackawanna RR/Minutes, 1960-1961 (Reel 5)
- The Development and Validation of a test of creative ability -- Harris, Richard H. (1955) (Reel 6)
- Minutes of the Joint Meeting of the State Lighting Committee -- April 7, 1914, Massachusetts (Reel 7)
- A Study of Productive efficiency with different ratios of direct and indirect light, for some total illumination -- Geis, E, Allphin, William (1925) (Reel 8)
- The Nature and Function of Authority -- Roelofs, Howard Dyksma (1925) (Reel 9)
- The Development of a test of creativity in engineering -- Harris, Douglas (1959) (Reel 10)